<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <packageId>saloid.AdvancedRaiders</packageId>
  <author>saloid</author>
  <name>Advanced raiders</name>
  <description>Adds new raider types and some related items.
    \n
    \n -Hey Ron, those tribespeople are trying to raid us again.
    \n -Nah, whatever, they won't pass through our killbox.
    \n -One of them just resurrected his buddy. 
    \n -What? 
    \n -They also brought a warg and two bears with them. And a pack of boomrats.
    \n -Oh, okay. We just have to kill or down about half of them and they will back off, right?
    \n -We already did. Looks like this guy in red shouting out weird words keeps them fighting.
    \n -Damn... But turrets will handle them anyway.
    \n -They won't. Broken by some guy during previous raid. Some even turned against us.
    \n -Why haven't anyone repaired them?
    \n -A sadistic merc beat up our only builder and it looks like he got PTSD. He is smashing walls in his room right now.
    \n -Use the doomsday rocket then!
    \n -I wasted it on some really tough guy with minigun during the same raid. 
    \n -Well, at least you've put it to the right use.
    \n -How to say... he was just downed and his friend injected him some red fluid. He just became stronger and angrier.
    \n
    \n I strongly recommend dont drop items mod (https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1778821244) to use with this one. Or without, it is cool by itself.
    \n Also you shold set enemy death on downed chance for about 50% or less. Merc medics need someone to "heal" after all.
    \n
    \n Please send your suggestions and report any bugs (I bet there is ton of them) and grammar mistakes you find. 
  </description>
  <supportedVersions>
    <!-- used by version check warning -->
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>